



CURRENT POSITION:Technical Director,
Centra Australia Pty Ltd

QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor of Engineering (Honours Class I)

Master of Business Administration

MEMBERSHIPS:

Engineers Australia Member No 389870

Australian Society for Concrete Paving

AREAS OF EXPERTISE:

Customer Service
Pavement Design
Asset Management
Risk Management
Project Management
Change Management
Construction Management
Traffic Engineering
Pavement Investigations
Pavement Dilapidation
Financial Management
Business Development

Quality Management

GREG WRIGHT CPEng BE (Hons 1) MBA MIFAust NFR

Career Overview

Greg is a Chartered Professional Engineer (CPEng) with a wealth of pavement engineering experience. He holds a Bachelor of (Civil) Engineering degree and a Master of Business Administration degree. He is listed on the <u>NER</u>.

Greg's leadership and technical expertise combined with his commitment to providing excellent customer service ensured the pavement design teams he led substantially contributed towards the successful delivery of large capex infrastructure projects such as the \$4.5B Brisbane Airport Link project, the \$3.8B Victorian Desalination Plant, the \$3.2B Clem 7 motorway project, the \$1.1B Lane Cove motorway project, the \$2.0B Ipswich Motorway upgrade project and the \$1.5B Port Botany Expansion project.

Greg led the Thiess John Holland pavement design team during the tender design phase of the \$2.65 billion North Connex project and advised Queensland Department of Transport and Main Roads regarding aligning their asphalt, aggregate and bitumen technical standards and test methods with those of Roads and Maritime Services.

Greg prepared asset management plans for the \$60million M2 Motorway pavement resurfacing plan, the \$15 million Highland Highway pavement rehabilitation plan and the \$600 million Westgate Freeway project.

Greg also contributed to the successful development and delivery of several other major infrastructure projects, such as, the Sapphire to Woolgoolga Pacific Highway upgrade, Port Botany Expansion, E2U and M2 Motorway Upgrade projects.

Greg led the pavement design teams for the \$3.8B Victorian Desalination Plant, the \$2.7B Clem 7 tunnel project and \$1.1B Lane Cove project and verified the \$2.0B lpswich Motorway upgrade and \$1.5B Port Botany Expansion projects.

Greg managed the delivery of road improvement projects such as the Pacific Highway carriageway duplication at Wyoming, the upgrade of the intersection of Lookout Road and McCaffery Drive, New Lambton Heights and the Hexham Contra flow Project.

Greg also project managed several other road improvement projects for the Roads and Traffic Management Section of RMS and ensured that each project was delivered on time, within budget and in accordance with stakeholder requirements.

Greg managed the delivery of six consecutive sealed road pavement management programmes for Hornsby Shire Council's between January 1995 and January 2001.

Career History

2013—Current	Centra Australia—Technical Director
2013—2013	HYDER Consulting—Associate Technical Director
2011—2012	AECOM—Associate Director
2005—2011	Parsons Brinckerhoff (PB)—Principal Engineer
2003—2005	Kellogg Brown & Root (KBR)—Project Supervisor
2001—2003	Connell Wagner (CW)—Senior Engineer
1995—2001	Hornsby Shire Council—Pavement Engineer
1989—1994	Cessnock City Council—Planning & Design Manager
1984—1989	Lake Macquarie City Council—Senior Engineer

